so a couple Summers back I was in high
school and I'm looking for just like a
crappy summer job you know something to
just hold me over and you have like the
jobs you want and then you have like
like the subway tier I call it it works
on two levels because Subways are below
the ground and because the restaurant
Subway is not a place you want to
work why it's called the subway here
anyway I like I didn't hear back from
any of these places and like
after a week of not hearing back from
Pizza Pie Cafe there's some part of
you there's some part of you that really
wants to believe that this is all just
like a weird six sense thing that's
happening you know you've actually been
dead for a
month I actually had a thought crossed
my mind this summer when I was like well
maybe something just killed me and I
didn't notice you know like thinking was
dead was easier for me to
accept than the fact that pizza pie cafe
did not want to interview me
even it's not a good
feeling